suiteblanco.com 2016-05-05

# Privacy policy

This Privacy Policy stipulates how personal data is handled on the www.blanco.com (hereinafter the " **Site** ").

By accessing the site a person is considered a user (hereinafter " **User** ") and by doing so claims to be aware and, if applicable, accept all the conditions in this Privacy Policy. The Site service provision is limited in duration to the time during which the user remains connected to the Site or any of the services it offers. The user must therefore carefully read this Privacy Policy every time he or she intends to use the Site, since the policy can be modified at any time.

##  1.COLLECTION, PROCESSING AND USE OF PERSONAL DATA 

In compliance with the provisions of Law 15/1999 of 13 December, regarding the Protection of Personal Data (hereinafter "Data Protection Act") and its implementation regulations, you are hereby informed that the data collected through this Site will be added to an automated personal data file for which the following companies may be accountable:

\- GLOBAL LEIVA, S.L. with registered office in Calle Juan de la Cierva, 60, 28936 Móstoles, tax identification number B-86817277 (hereinafter "GLOBAL LEIVA").

GLOBAL LEIVA is focused on the retail sale of fashion apparel and equipment, footwear, accessories, cosmetics, personal care products, household products, consumer electronics and other consumer products and services marketed under Blanco name or in Blanco shops. The company responsible for the file will be GLOBAL LEIVA, or both companies simultaneously, as expressly stated in this Privacy Policy or in any given data collection form.

Your data will be processed with the aim of addressing the various types of relationships that may arise between users of the Site and GLOBAL LEIVA as a result of the requests, negotiations, purchases or arrangements to which the corresponding data collection form refers. The data handled by GLOBAL LEIVA are those collected through the corresponding data forms and, where appropriate, those that are collected or obtained later for specific aims in any given case.

All fields marked with an asterisk (*) in any of the forms must be filled in, and the omission of any of them may make it impossible for us to provide the services requested.

The Site currently features the following data collection points:

\- **"Log in"** Section: To be able to shop online on our Site, users will need to be registered as Registered Users. To this end, given its responsibility for the file, GLOBAL LEIVA will request a series of personal data through a registration form. These data, together with those obtained from purchases made, will be processed with the aim of allowing online shopping and servicing customer orders. GLOBAL LEIVA may also process user data in order to contact registered users in the event of any kind of incidence during order or payment processing. GLOBAL LEIVA may collect new data or confirm data already collected when necessary for the fulfilment of a contract, fraud prevention or for conducting surveys on the quality of products and services. Additionally, GLOBAL LEIVA can treat your personal data used to make purchases on the Site for commercial profiling and advertising and to offer retail products and services that may be of interest to you in apparel and equipment fashion, footwear, accessories, cosmetics, personal care, household products, consumer electronics, computer products and other consumer products and services marketed under Blanco or sold in Blanco shops.

By marking the box "I want to receive communication via e-mail or equivalent means", the user expressly authorises GLOBAL LEIVA to send these marketing communications by e-mail or equivalent means (SMS or MMS).

This registration form may also request consent for a number of other purposes that do not relate directly to the purchase. If you do not agree with these additional uses, check or uncheck the box provided for this purpose, as appropriate.

\- **"Newsletter"** Section: By submitting the relevant form, the user expressly consents to GLOBAL LEIVA, as holder of the data, to send them their corporate newsletter by any means, including electronic means, and to offer products and services that may be of interest relating to apparel or equipment fashion, footwear, accessories, cosmetics, personal care, household products, consumer electronics, computer products and other consumer products and services marketed under Blanco or sold in Blanco stores.

\- **"Press"** : section: By submitting the subscription request form via e-mail to press@blanco.com, the User expressly consents to GLOBAL LEIVA, as holder of the data, sending press releases by any means, including electronic means, issued by any of the companies who have business partnerships with GLOBAL LEIVA for the retail sale of fashion apparel and equipment, footwear, accessories, cosmetics, personal care, household products, consumer electronics and other consumer products and services marketed under Blanco or sold in Blanco shops. Users may unsubscribe from these electronic messages at any time by requesting to unsubscribe via the following e-mail address: press@blanco.com

\- **"Work with us"Section** : By sending your CV by e-mail, you consent to the data in your CV as well as those collected during telephone calls or screening tests to be used for the sole purpose of verifying and evaluating your candidacy for the current or future selection process that may be carried out by GLOBAL LEIVA as responsible for the file, as well as other companies that may have business relationships with GLOBAL LEIVA for the retail sale of fashion apparel or equipment, footwear, accessories, cosmetics, personal care, home products, consumer electronics and other consumer products and services marketed under Blanco or sold in Blanco shops.

Furthermore, by submitting your data via the forms provided or via e-mail to the corresponding addresses, you declare that the information and data provided are accurate and truthful, and that you are over 14 years old. Site services are not aimed at children under 14 so we have no provisions for parental consent under any circumstances.

GLOBAL LEIVA will keep users data for the periods stipulated by law for every case and without prejudice to your right of cancellation.

##  2\. COMMUNICATION OR TRANSFER OF DATA 

Data collected on the Website may be communicated to other Group companies or companies that have business relationships with GLOBAL LEIVA for the retail sale of fashion apparel or equipment, footwear, accessories, cosmetics, personal care products, home products, consumer electronics and other consumer products and services marketed under Blanco or sold in Blanco shops, for the same purposes as those specified in this Data Protection Policy.

##  3\. EXERCISE OF ACCESS, RECTIFICATION, CANCELLATION AND OPPOSITION RIGHTS 

Users may at any moment exercise their rights of access, rectification, cancellation and opposition to the processing of their data, and may revoke their consent in the terms stipulated by law, by writing to the address indicated in paragraph 1 or the following e-mail address: clientes@blanco.com and attaching a copy of a valid ID.

##  4\. OPPOSITION TO THE SENDING OF ADVERTISING 

Users may object to the sending of advertising messages by sending an email to the following address: clientes@blanco.com (Spain). To unsubscribe from e-mail advertising list, users may also access the Newsletter section of the Site and enter their e-mail address in the "Unsubscribe" section.
